i created a brownie brand
sales are growing
but not at the speed I need
so i decided to create three plans
and today I will show you
first of them
put the music there
then it already starts
coming
it was bad the delay eh
moleque
this one is mine
can only release
that's why it doesn't break more than my idea mano
we have to have a call to action
for people to see this marketing
see this campaign there to get children's attention
in the long term it opens
I think a really big fan like that
for you to put an effect
can you cheat
what we need
let's go to the points
i need to take these pictures man
building this strategic plan
now we will
perform
is recording
already goes there
I already show you
maaf
1 good visual angle
understood
we're back here in the tent now bro
we have to run away
now we need to prepare this
as soon as we can shoot this tomorrow morning old man
got good
my god asshole
the idea is to spread this
we can put that from there
tomorrow morning
then we already have what to do tomorrow
our intelligence
it's very
this is too important for us to use
it's exactly that bro
it's exactly that
I think lame if you don't show it
but the video is ending,
it's true
until tomorrow
caraca hand
every time i try to show the guys something
bro and then the video ends
there it's tomorrow
can you see